[Characters, behaviors, places, organizations,
professions, or events shown in the series
are entirely fictional,
solely for the purpose of entertainment,
with no intention to instruct
or promote any kind of behavior;
viewer discretion is advised]
If you still want to capture Krating...
Master In's daughter...
Who is she?
Master Bulan.
If you do not...
come before me tonight,
do not expect...
a peaceful slumber.
I have to go home with the bullets,
no matter what it takes.
Could you have me
transferred to Phop Phra?
Yes, Dad.
I've had a talk with them.
Go ahead and report yourself.
As for the documents,
I'll forward them later.
Thank you, Dad.
Right,
Dad.
If...
I need your help with something,
would that be possible?
If it's about Mom,
don't worry at all, Peem.
I'll take care of it.
Alright.
I just don't want to be
another one of Mom's worries.
What happened to Phu...
has already caused her enough sorrow.
Peem, my dear,
whatever you have in mind,
I won't stop you.
[Phop Phra Police Station]
But you have to promise me
you'll take good care of yourself.
Yes,
I promise.
I'll go ahead and introduce her.
This is Police Lieutenant Phitcha Ruechakun.
She's a detective from Bangkok.
You can call me "Peem."
I'll be temporarily stationed here
to investigate a human trafficking case.
And if the clues align with
the intelligence I've received,
the suspect might be using
the international border
to transport the victims
to neighboring countries.
I'm not here only to help the victims,
but I'm here...
to eradicate the ones responsible,
no matter where they might be hiding.
Anyway...
please take care of me.
We can take care of your heart, too.
Your wife's gonna come
cuss you out again, Sarge.
That day when you were seeing
that watermelon vendor lady,
I heard you still haven't sorted things out.
Jeez...
I was just being playful, Chief.
I love my family
just as much as you love yours.
Don't hold it against him, Lieutenant.
If you have any questions,
ask the sergeant.
He's been married and settled here
for more than a decade.
He also transferred here,
just like you did.
Yes, and I found love here at Phop Phra.
That's that.
If there's something you wanna know
or anywhere you wanna go,
ask him.
Yes, sir.
Our sub-district here is small,
nowhere near as busy as Bangkok.
Someone as skilled as you
will adapt in no time.
As for the case that brought you here,
I would like you to be very careful.
Every area has its own etiquette,
especially when it comes to
matters related to neighboring countries,
which are even more sensitive.
I hope you understand.
Yes,
I understand.
More importantly,
your father instructed me
to take good care of you.
So, don't put yourself in danger.
I am here to work on a case.
There's no need for you
to give me special treatment.
I just don't want to have
any problems with your parents.
Anyway, if you find out anything,
report it to me first.
Do not act on your own.
This is an order.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
Then, get back to work.
Sarge.
Yes?
Show the lieutenant her desk.
Yes, sir!
This way, Lieutenant.
♫Along with ghostly spirits
hounding relentlessly,♫
♫May the maras be ravaged
and perish completely♫
♫Vindictive spirits, tyrannical psyches,♫
♫Meant to betray, slaughter, and invade,♫
♫Were any souls to brush
against my karmic soulmate,♫
♫They shall bury the thought
of returning to their realm♫
♫With incantation and virtue as shield,♫
♫At my feet,
they shall surrender and kneel,♫
♫Chanting, "Sadhu," of their own will♫
This is the desk
for our beautiful lieutenant.
Peace and quiet,
but not private.
You don't have to call me
"Beautiful Lieutenant."
Just "Lieutenant Peem" is fine.
Copy.
Oh!
Uh...
I'm going on patrol this afternoon.
If you're interested...
after lunch,
meet me downstairs.
Alright, Sarge.
Alright.
Make yourself comfortable, Sarge.
- Yes.
- Don't be nervous.
Alright.
Oh, my, it's so hot.
That looks delicious, Sarge.
I haven't eaten it yet.
Your table's full.
Hello.
What is Master doing here?
I've only seen her
at major merit-making ceremonies.
Sarge.
Yes?
Welcome Master for me, okay?
Get her some water, too.
Yes, sir.
I have to take care
of something real quick.
Alright.
Sarge,
I'll give this to her myself.
Alright.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Why didn't you close it properly?
That's careless of you.
You came here to see me?
Could it be that...
you've decided
to help me with the bullets?
I made you breakfast,
but you left in such haste
without eating it.
So I have prepared
lunch for you in a tiffin.
In this tiffin...
there is roasted laab
and kaeng hang ley with pork.
I do not know what food you favor,
so I brought everything I had made.
You came all the way here
just because of this?
I made this especially for you.
You know how serious I am about this.
My little brother is at death's door,
lying in a hospital bed,
but you're treating this
like some kind of joke.
If you don't intend to help,
please stop messing with my head.
Do I look like
I am here to play?
If I truly did not intend to help,
then why did I close
the sanctum to come see you?
Forget me messing with your head.
The restless spirits
hounding you all the way here
might soon madden you
into oblivion.
I have never regarded this
as a debt of gratitude.
Had you not been someone
I yearn for so deeply,
you, cocky officer,
would never set foot in my sanctum.
I made these dishes for you,
but if you do not care for them,
throw them away.
So, as long as I eat it, that's enough?
Fine.
Okay.
I ate it.
Happy?
Is it not to your taste?
I'm full.
I don't eat breakfast
or a heavy meal for lunch.
I don't eat again...
until dinner.
Besides,
I'm not in the mood to eat in peace.
If you do not force yourself to eat,
how will you have
the strength to arrest criminals?
It's not anyone's concern.
Master,
please come this way.
Lieutenant,
these are the files for the local case.
Yes, Sarge.
Whoa...
Didn't you say you were gonna eat
when you go on patrol?
Where is she, Lieutenant?
Has she already left?
What do you mean, Sarge?
Well, your girlfriend, of course.
What girlfriend, Sarge?
I am single.
Don't, Lieutenant.
I'm eagle-eyed.
Nothing escapes my sight.
You should put
those skills to use at work, Sarge.
Aha.
Not on my personal matters.
Sharp-tongued.
No wonder you're from Bangkok.
By the way,
you know Master?
I saw you talking in the chief's room.
Sarge,
you asked me to go on patrol?
Yes.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
By the way,
where's the restroom at this station?
I want to change
into something more flexible.
Over there.
There's a clean one and a not-so-clean one.
Anything will do.
Come on, Sarge.
We're wasting our time.
There's the suspect's shit, too.
And mine.
What a load of BS, Sarge.
Yes, ma'am.
This area borders Myanmar,
Phop Phra included.
People here come from
diverse ethnic backgrounds.
They're Thai,
Bamar, Karen,
S'gaw Karen,
Haw Chinese,
Akha,
and Hmong.
There are also
the dark arts and black magic.
There are Northeasterners here, too.
Eat up, Lieutenant.
It's really delicious, Sarge.
Chai!
Long time no see.
You're getting chubbier.
Well, I've made a bit of money.
I've been doing business
on the other side.
Here you go.
Take some.
Ever heard of them?
Sengphae and halawa.
I've heard of them, but never tried them.
They taste like our khanom krok.
Sengphae is made with glutinous rice,
while halawa is made with rice.
They're hard to come by.
I'm giving you some.
Try them for me.
And...
share some with this sugar.
Whoa, whoa.
She's a new officer at the station.
You're making me look bad.
Go. Run along now.
Fine, I'm going.
Let's meet up and drink sometime, Sarge.
Uh-uh, not drinking.
Lieutenant.
Go ahead, Sarge.
I don't really eat desserts.
What did...
you just do?
Sarge, why did you pass the dessert
between your legs?
I've already told you
that no one can be trusted here.
There are both magic and the dark arts.
This is what you do to ward it off.
Sarge.
Sarge!
This isn't funny, Sarge!
It's so good
my eyes roll back, Lieutenant.
Look at you,
messing around like this.
If this really happened one day,
what would you do?
Screw it all.
You joke about everything.
This is just to break the ice.
Sis!
Someone wants you
to check on your daughter at school.
They're saying that
she's possessed!
Sarge...
Sir, I'll be back to pay.
Lieutenant.
Kids, make way.
Make way.
This way, Master.
This brat has desecrated me.
I will bring death upon her!
Go.
Do not harm an innocent child.
She did this to me!
I will tear her to pieces!
She must die!
Hold her.
If she gets away, it will be dangerous.
Pleng.
Pleng, my baby!
Pleng!
Pleng, what's happening to you?!
Pleng, baby!
Master!
Pleng took out
a Thai dancer figurine to play with
and...accidentally broke its glass cover
when she put it back.
Pleng.
Pleng, dear!
Pleng!
Oh, alas.
Never before have I seen one depart.
Would fallen spirits
triumph over the living?
By the sacred power of Namo Buddhaya.
What is this, Sarge?
It seems...
she's possessed;
otherwise,
Master wouldn't
have been summoned here.
This doesn't seem right to me, Sarge.
What do you mean?
Can't you see she's being possessed?
Master is using a ritual knife
to exorcise it.
See? It's squirming.
"Exorcise," my ass!
You can clearly see
that the kid's being assaulted!
(Incanting)
- Excuse me.
- Lieutenant! Lieutenant!
(Incanting)
Miss!
Who are you?
Why are you interrupting the ritual?!
What ritual?
You saw that the kid
was convulsing so badly
that she couldn't control herself.
And what kind of teacher are you, huh?
Why didn't you take her to the hospital?!
Goodness!
Argh! My heart is bursting!
Are you out of your mind?!
My daughter is possessed!
Why would we take her to the hospital?!
Master!
- Master, please help my child.
- You are all going to die!
- Master! Please help my child.
Please help her again, Master!
- Get a grip, ma'am!
- My heart is about to break, Master!
Get a grip!
Don't you see what's happening to her?!
It's because I do!
I've raised her since birth!
Just by looking into her eyes,
I know that's not my daughter!
- Pleng...
- Fine!
If ghosts are real,
come get what you want from me!
Don't take it out on a child!
Pleng! My baby!
Pleng!
Master, help!
Sarge, call an ambulance!
Sarge!
Master!
I am not your child!
Lieutenant,
are you okay?
I'm fine, Sarge.
Please let Master continue the ritual!
Pleng, baby! Pleng!
Pleng!
Master!
Master...
I'm begging you, please help her, Master.
Please...
Ma'am,
put this necklace on her.
I am a cop.
She will be safe.
Please trust me, ma'am.
Please do it.
Pleng.
Pleng, dear.
Pleng! Pleng.
Pleng...
May the deities protect you.
Come back to Mommy, baby.
Sarge, call an ambulance.
Lieutenant, the ambulance is here!
Alright.
- Ma'am, let's go.
- Let's go.
Alright.
- Come on. Coming through.
- Kids,
go back to class. Quick.
Please move aside.
I have never minded
that you do not believe in it,
but do not interrupt my ritual.
It is disrespectful
to my masters and my sacred arts.
When afflictions come your way,
even I cannot come to your rescue.
Prove it to me, then.
I'd also love to know
if you could really banish ghosts
if they were real.
[Phop Phra Police Station]
"But do not interrupt my ritual.
It is disrespectful
to my masters and my sacred arts."
"When afflictions come your way,
even I cannot come to your rescue."
Sarge,
how's the kid?
Well...
some bruises here and there.
They've given her tranquilizers.
She's in the hospital right now.
Mm,
that's good.
Uh...
By the way,
how are you doing?
Weren't you bitten?
Wait...
You've been slapped, too.
But I do think you're special, Lieutenant.
How so, Sarge?
Ever since I moved here,
this is the first time
I've seen her
slap someone that hard.
So...
what's this master of yours usually like?
Could you tell me about her?
This lady...
she's the real one.
She's legit.
She's the best in all of Phop Phra.
How so?
She's beautiful
and capable.
When it comes to the Great Charm Yantras,
she's second to none.
She's that good.
So...
this master of yours
doesn't have a single flaw?
She doesn't.
Though...
she would only tattoo women
because she dislikes men.
How about
I take you to her sanctum when we're free?
Enough, Sarge.
If you're going to talk about
Master Bulan again,
I'd rather not listen.
I don't want to hear
about anything that can't be proven,
especially her arts.
Uh, Lieutenant.
Lieutenant, Lieutenant...
You wanna eat it?
Yes.
It's all yours.
Thank you.
Sarge,
how can you...
believe in something like this?
Seeing is believing.
You have to witness it yourself
to realize it's real.
My hands are real shaky.
Mm.
Which restaurant made this?
I'll give them my business.
Mm.
Almost forgot.
The chief
left the key to the residence for you.
By the way, you...
don't have a home here
or...
live with someone, right?
No.
I'm not living with anyone.
I sleep alone.
Serves you right.
Looking like that,
someone like you will stay single
for the rest of your life.
You're mid.
Just stay single for life.
Can't even compare to my wifey.
Is your wife that pretty?
What?!
My wife?
I thought my room
was just like any other room.
But when my child walked past it,
the kid said there was a god in my room
because that's what my wife had cried out.
"Oh, my God."
"My God!"
Wow....
We go at it every day.
grabbing by the hair,
slapping,
lamps to the head, and all that.
Every darn day.
Just cut it, Sarge.
I am sorry, Mommy.
But Mom...
Keep still.
Do not feign concern.
Let her see it for herself.
[18 missing-person cases in Phop Phra]
[Recurring incidents]
[9 cases in Bangkok;
Pat is among the victims]
["Master Bulan"]
Master Bulan...
I have never minded
that you do not believe in it,
but do not interrupt my ritual.
It is disrespectful
to my sacred masters and my arts.
When afflictions come your way,
even I cannot come to your rescue.
Peem...
Where did that come from?
I came from a faraway golden land,
crossing the river
that flowed from the North.
What a long odyssey.
What the hell?
You have challenged me.
I will bring death upon you!
My hair cascades.
My eyes are filled with nothing but sorrow.
From this breath on,
we shall never be severed.
You shall come with me!
Never.
Keep your nose out of it.
Return to where you came from.
I have been waiting for so long.
Give her to me.
Whichever ghost dares touch her,
right then
shall I burn its spirit to dust.
Leave!
♫Along with ghostly spirits
hounding relentlessly,♫
♫May the maras be ravaged
and perish completely♫
♫Vindictive spirits, tyrannical psyches,♫
♫Meant to betray, slaughter, and invade,♫
♫Were any souls to brush
against my karmic soulmate,♫
♫They shall bury the thought
of returning to their realm♫
Dear vital spirits,
wherever you may be,
may you return.
I will return it tomorrow.
This fabric,
isn't it expensive?
From now on,
do not commit such desecration again.
I have warned you before.
Should you play a hero,
you will be afflicted.
From now on,
what will happen to her?
Will she still wait for someone she loves?
How did you feel at the time, Lieutenant?
At the time...
I felt heartache
and sorrow.
She would still wait,
though pain or sorrow befell her.
She would endure it all,
waiting for the day
she finds joy,
if only for a little while.
You seem to understand her so well.
I'm sorry for the chaos I caused.
Pay it no mind.
From now on,
you must keep your wits about you.
Everything I have done for you
is for your own sake.
You're also alone,
so how come...
you always have to protect me,
not to mention...
perform exorcisms for people?
Why?
I linger here
for my karmic soulmate.
Did they disappear?
Or...
are they somewhere else, working?
♫Mantra of love, please take the lead♫
♫So our hearts are sworn by♫
♫I shall love and commit♫
♫Until the day I die♫
♫As long as I shall breathe♫
♫I will be your karmic soulmate♫
♫Until my being fades♫
♫May sacred mantras bind us together♫
My dearest,
stay here with me.
I...
I'm sorry.
♫Mantra of love, please take the lead♫
♫So our hearts are sworn by♫
♫I shall love and commit♫
♫Until the day I die♫
♫As long as I shall breathe♫
♫I will be your karmic soulmate♫
♫Until my being fades♫
♫May sacred mantras bind us together♫
[Been put under a love spell]
[The signs of being under a love spell,
or Ya Faed charm,
can be seen through significant changes
in behavior and emotion]
[For Saneh Ya Faed, beware of food]
At the station...
I was just going to wake you up.
Where are you rushing off to?
Come here.
I woke up before daybreak to cook.
No, I'm fine, thanks.
I already told you
I don't eat breakfast.
Just have a taste.
What are these photos?
These photos confirm clues about Krating.
Right now, the guy
is hiding out in Mae Sot.
So why haven't you
told me about this, sir?
Do you have any accommodations
you can recommend?
I do.
I'm sorry, but we have no vacancies.
Why...
did you decide to move to Phop Phra?
A place called home
is where your loved ones await.
♫It's not that I don't feel it♫
♫It's not that I'm cold-hearted♫
♫For the love you've given♫
♫It's because
it feels too good to be true,♫
♫So much so that I doubt if it's true♫
♫If it's smoke and mirrors,
a dream that lingers♫
♫Deeply swayed by love,
all while shaken with dread,♫
♫Scared that it's not love
after all in the end♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫Can you so gently give me some time,♫
♫For me to ponder what's on my mind?♫
♫I would hate to be wavering
when love binds♫
♫Deeply swayed by love,
all while shaken with dread,♫
♫Scared that it's not love
after all in the end♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫Tell me it's not an illusion
you beautifully created♫
♫Don't let my heart suffer
and ache inside this cage♫
♫I would do anything just to escape♫
♫What if, between us,♫
♫It's nothing but a perfect illusion,♫
♫Nothing short of deception?♫
♫What I've kept hidden for ages,♫
♫Do you know how painful it is♫
♫To keep my heart locked away in a cage?♫
♫I don't want to lock my heart away♫
♫I wish you'd know one day♫